{
	"word_title": {
		"message": "Word Online"
	},
	"word_description": {
		"message": "Create, edit and share Word documents. Work with others on shared projects, in real-time."
	},
	"excel_title": {
		"message": "Excel Online"
	},
	"excel_description": {
		"message": "Create, edit and share Excel spreadsheets. Work with others on shared projects, in real-time."
	},
	 "powerpoint_title": {
		"message": "PowerPoint Online"
	},
	"powerpoint_description": {
		"message": "Create, edit and share PowerPoint presentations.  Work with others on shared projects, in real-time."
	},
	"onenote_title": {
		"message": "OneNote Online"
	},
	"onenote_description": {
		"message": "All your notes—in one place and with you, anywhere.  Get things done with your friends, family, classmates, and colleagues."
	},
	"office_online_description": {
		"message": "Office Online combines the most common Office features and real-time co-authoring capabilities so teams at school and home can collaborate on shared documents, presentations and spreadsheets. 
Office Online also works with the Office applications installed on your desktop, so you can choose how you want to work. Use Office Online to dynamically collaborate with real time co-authoring, or if you already have Office, continue working with the full power of Word, PowerPoint, and Excel applications installed on your PC or Mac. 
Getting started is simple; 
• Create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations online or with a desktop version of Office
• Save them online in OneDrive
• Share with others to collaborate in real-time      
"
	}
}












